Shaili Srivastava

Java Backend Developer



✓ Srivastavshailii@gmail.com

← +919335293455
• Basti, Uttar Pradesh

in Shaili Srivastava 🕟 Shaili-Srivastava

▶ Portfolio



Professional Summary

A skilled and passionate Backend Developer with problem solving mindset. 1000+ hours of hands-on coding experience. Looking forward to working in an IT company where I can utilize and enhance my skills.

Technical Skills

- Java | Spring Boot | MySQL | Hibernate | AWS
- HTML | CSS | JavaScript
- Data Structure and Algorithm

Soft Skills

- Communication Skill
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Team Worker
- Remote Collaboration

Education

Java Backend Development , Masai School, Full-Time , Feb 2022 - Present

Master's of Social Work, Rajarishi Tondon Open University Allahabad 07/2019-07/2011

Bachelor's of Science, Siddharth University Kapilvast India 08/2016 - 07/2019

Projects

Clone of YOOX 2

Github Repo -

https://github.com/arulxavierax/Project-U2-Y00X

It is an E - Commerce website from where you can purchase clothes, accessories and footwear.

Tech Stack -

HTML | CSS | JavaScript

Area of Responsbility -

- Created the login and signup page
- Helped in the building of home page.

A collaborative project built by a team of 5 members completed within 5 days.

Sephora NNNOW Clone 🛮

Github Repo - https://github.com/krajeet35/Project--miscreant-punishment-3547 □

It is an E-Commerce website where we can purchase cosmetic products of different different brands.

Tech Stack -

HTML | CSS | JavaScript

Area of Responsbility -

- Created the sub-category section.
- · Sorting and filtering functionality on the subcategory page.

A collaborative project built by a team of 5 members completed within 5 days.

Professional Experience

AVOC - Associate, Amazon 🗷

02/2022 - 06/2022

Responsbilities:- To watch video of the stowing activity in a fulfillment center, make best use of the human judgement using Attention To Detail and Thinking skills.

Customer Support Executive, *Startek* ✓

06/2022 - 10/2022 | India

Responsbilities:- To resolve customer's querries and provide proper resolution using Problem Solving and Proffesional Communication skills.



Internships

Social Media Marketing, Aashman Foundation May 2021 - Sept 2021

Human Resource Management, Aashman Foundation May 2021 - Sept 2021